Privacy Policy

NOTICE AND DISCLAIMER: Digital cartography can be inaccurate and incomplete to some extent. The availability and accuracy of GPS and related services are dependent, among other things, on wireless networks and satellite systems. They may not function in all areas or at all times. Therefore never rely solely on the aforementioned material and services e.g. for essential communications like emergencies. This product and its contents are made for non-commercial private use only. This product should not be used by the driver of a motor vehicle while driving. Always keep your hands free to operate a vehicle while driving. Obey all local laws. Your first consideration while driving should be road safety. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, General Magic, its subsidiaries and licensors hereby disclaim all liability arising out of any use of this product and its contents.

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs how we, Magic Earth (“we”, “our” or “us”) use, collect and store information pertaining to you (“User”, “you”), user of Magic Earth mobile application (“App”).

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and contact us if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy explains:  
• What information we collect and why we collect it.  
• Your rights and choices with regard to that information.  
• The steps we take to protect that information.  
• Limitations with regard to third party websites and content.  
• How we transfer the information.  
• How we may make changes to our Privacy Policy.  
• How you may contact us.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY WE COLLECT IT  
“Personal Information” means any information about an identified or identifiable individual.  
**The information we collect is kept only for the purposes stated below, and for a limited period of time, after which it is destroyed.**

We use the information about you that is automatically generated while you use our services, but we do not collect it. In many cases data is generated inherent to you using a computing device or inherent to transmitting data over computer networks, such as the Internet. This data includes IP-addresses, date and time of your requests, operating system type. We may also use real-time geo-location information of your device, search reference geographic position, routing and search preferences, crash reports and app version installed.

**We do not store Personal Information generated automatically while you use our services**.

We may collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect information such as language, time-zone, search requests and routing requests, so we can improve the user experience and our services.

We may use the information we collect for the following reasons:  
(i) Provide our services  
• We use your information to provide navigation services, best route choices, traffic information, map updates, alerts, weather data and to provide information about locations on the map.

(ii) Maintain and improve our services  
• We also use your information to ensure our app is working as intended, for technical diagnostics, to detect fraud and abuse and to improve our services. For example, we may use the route information to improve the accuracy of the navigation data.

(iii) Communicate with you  
• We may use your information to communicate with you through push notifications. For example, we may contact you to provide service-related messages such as notifications, confirmations, updates, and security alerts.   
• We may keep a record of your requests in order to help solve any issues you might be facing;

(iv) Protect Magic Earth, our users, the public and for Legal reasons  
• To enforce the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy;  
• To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies under any applicable law  
• To detect abuse and illegal activity; to detect and prevent fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity theft and other illegal activities and misuse of our services;  
• To handle breakdowns and malfunctions;  
• To take any action in any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and the App, or between you and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with the App;  
• For purposes provided under this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use;  
• To help improve the safety and reliability of our App.  
• To create anonymous data (where such data does not enable the identification of a specific user).

**A list with the information that we use, collect and store, along with the period of time for which this is retained, can be found [here](https://www.magicearth.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/MagicEarth-User-Data-Privacy-20240703.pdf).**

We do not sell or rent the information to marketers or third parties. We may, however, share or disclose the information as follows:  
• Members of our group. We may share the information to any members of our group, subsidiaries and branch offices, to which it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose the information in order to carry out the above-mentioned information processing purposes.  
• Compliance with laws and law enforcement. We will share the information if we, in our good faith judgment, believe it is necessary to: (i) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; (ii) comply with laws and legal process (including valid subpoenas, court orders, or government requests); (iii) take precautions against liability and protect the property, rights, and safety of our App users or others as required or permitted by law; (iii) enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements; (iv) prevent or stop activity we believe to be illegal, fraudulent, abusive, unethical or legally actionable; and (v) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, the security or integrity of our App or equipment used to make the App available, or any other technical issues.  
• Other Disclosures. We may disclose the information in other ways when we have your consent to do so.

YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES  
Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the data we collect about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your information, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. You also have the right to withdraw your consent to the collection of your Personal Information. You may at any time stop the collection of your information via the settings of your device, or by uninstalling the App. Note however that if you exercise your right of blocking or deletion, if you decline to share certain information with us, or if you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionalities of the App.

To exercise your rights and choices to your Personal Information, please contact us by using the contact details provide below under “Our Contact Information”.

INFORMATION SECURITY  
We maintain technical and organizational measures intended to protect the information that we collect against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage.

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES AND CONTENT  
Our App may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from Magic Earth. Linked websites may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the revised policy and the revised version will be effective when it is posted.

OUR CONTACT INFORMATION  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and the way in which we handle the information that we collect, or to exercise your rights and choices, please contact us at privacy@magicearth.com.

Magic Earth, Netherlands, De Smalle Zijde 3, NL-3903 LL, Veenendaal

Privacy Policy

NOTICE AND DISCLAIMER: Digital cartography can be inaccurate and incomplete to some extent. The availability and accuracy of GPS and related services are dependent, among other things, on wireless networks and satellite systems. They may not function in all areas or at all times. Therefore never rely solely on the aforementioned material and services e.g. for essential communications like emergencies. This product and its contents are made for non-commercial private use only. This product should not be used by the driver of a motor vehicle while driving. Always keep your hands free to operate a vehicle while driving. Obey all local laws. Your first consideration while driving should be road safety. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, General Magic, its subsidiaries and licensors hereby disclaim all liability arising out of any use of this product and its contents.

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs how we, General Magic B.V. (“General Magic”, “Company”, “we”, “our” or “us”) use, collect and store information pertaining to you (“User”, “you”), visitor of [www.magicearth.com](https://www.magicearth.com/) (“Website”) and/or Magic Earth mobile application (“App”) (collectively referred to as the “Services”).

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and contact us if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy explains:  
• What information we collect and why we collect it.  
• Your rights and choices with regard to that information.  
• The steps we take to protect that information.  
• Limitations with regard to third party websites and content.  
• How we transfer your information.  
• How we may make changes to our Privacy Policy.  
• How you may contact us.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY WE COLLECT IT  
“Personal Information” means any information about an identified or identifiable individual. **The information is kept only for the purposes stated below, and for a limited period of time, after which it is destroyed.**

We use the Personal Information about you that is automatically generated while you use our Services, but we do not collect it. In many cases data is generated inherent to you using a computing device or inherent to transmitting data over computer networks, such as the Internet. This data includes IP-addresses, date and time of your requests, operating system type. We may also use real-time geo-location information of your device, search reference geographic position, routing and search preferences, crash reports and app version installed.

We do not store Personal Information generated automatically while you use our Services.

We may collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect information such as language, time-zone, search requests and routing requests, so we can improve the user experience and our Services.

We may use the Personal Information we collect through the Services for the following reasons:  
(i) Provide our Services  
• We use your information to provide navigation services, best route choices, traffic information, map updates, alerts, weather data and to provide information about locations on the map.

(ii) Maintain and improve our Services  
• We also use your information to ensure our Services are working as intended, for technical diagnostics, to detect fraud and abuse and to improve our Services. For example, we may use your route information to improve the accuracy of the navigation data.

(iii) Communicate with you  
• We may use your information to communicate with you through push notifications. For example, we may contact you to provide service-related messages such as notifications, confirmations, updates, and security alerts. Where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent to send you marketing communications by electronic means;  
• We may keep a record of your requests in order to help solve any issues you might be facing;

(iv) Protect Magic Earth, our users, the public and for Legal reasons  
• To enforce the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy;  
• To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies under any applicable law  
• To detect abuse and illegal activity; to detect and prevent fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity theft and other illegal activities and misuse of the Services;  
• To handle breakdowns and malfunctions;  
• To take any action in any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and the Services, or between you and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with the Services;  
• For purposes provided under this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use;  
• To help improve the safety and reliability of our Services.  
• To create anonymous data (where such data does not enable the identification of a specific user).

A list with the information that we use, collect and store, along with the period of time for which this is retained, can be found [here](https://www.magicearth.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/MagicEarth-User-Data-Privacy_20190329.pdf).

HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION  
We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to marketers or third parties. We may, however, share or disclose your Personal Information as follows:  
• Members of our group. We may share your Personal Information to any members of our group, subsidiaries and branch offices, to which it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your Personal Information in order to carry out the above-mentioned information processing purposes.  
• Compliance with laws and law enforcement. We will share your Personal Information if we, in our good faith judgment, believe it is necessary to: (i) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; (ii) comply with laws and legal process (including valid subpoenas, court orders, or government requests); (iii) take precautions against liability and protect the property, rights, and safety of our affiliates, our App users, or others as required or permitted by law; (iii) enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements; (iv) prevent or stop activity we believe to be illegal, fraudulent, abusive, unethical or legally actionable; and (v) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, the security or integrity of our App or equipment used to make the App available, or any other technical issues.  
• Business Transfers. If General Magic is involved in a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or bankruptcy, your Personal Information may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to an acquirer, or successor or assignee. Should such operation occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the acquirer to use your Personal Information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Following such operation, you may contact the entity to which we transferred your Personal Information with any inquiries concerning the processing of that information.  
• Other Disclosures. We may disclose your Personal Information in other ways when we have your consent to do so.

YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES  
Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access Personal Information may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. You also have the right to withdraw your consent to the collection of your Personal Information. You may at any time stop the collection of your location or contact information via the settings of your device, or by uninstalling the App. Note however that if you exercise your right of blocking or deletion, if you decline to share certain Personal Information with us, or if you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionalities of the App.

To exercise your rights and choices to your Personal Information, please contact us by using the contact details provide below under “Our Contact Information”.

INFORMATION SECURITY  
We maintain technical and organizational measures intended to protect the Personal Information we obtain about you through the App against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage.

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES AND CONTENT  
Our App may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from Magic Earth. Linked websites may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY  
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post the revised policy and the revised version will be effective when it is posted.

OUR CONTACT INFORMATION  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and the way in which we handle your Personal Information, or to exercise your rights and choices, please contact us at privacy@magicearth.com.

General Magic B.V., Netherlands, De Smalle Zijde 3, NL-3903 LL, Veenendaal

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarise yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions using the contact information elsewhere in this website.

Collection and Use of Personal Information  
Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with us or an affiliated company. We and our affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any queries you may have.

Here are some examples of the types of personal information we may collect and how we may use it.

What personal information we collect  
• When you create an account, register your products, apply for commercial credit, purchase a product, download a software update, contact us or participate in an online survey, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information.

• When you share your content with family and friends using our products, send gift certificates and products, or invite others to join you on our forums or blogs, we may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number.

• In the U.S., we may ask for your Social Security number (SSN) but only in limited circumstances such as when setting up an account.

How we use your personal information  
• The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on our latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by updating your preferences.

• We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our products, services, content and advertising, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes.

• From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with us, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

• We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications.

• If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information  
We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

• We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where a product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.

• We may collect information regarding customer activities on our website, and store and from our other products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

Cookies and Other Technologies  
Our website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

We and our partners may use cookies and other technologies in mobile advertising services to control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. If you do not want to receive ads with this level of relevance on your mobile device, you can opt out by accessing the following link on your Apple device: http://oo.apple.com or Android device using: https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en. If you opt out, you will continue to receive the same number of mobile ads, but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests. You may still see ads related to the content on a web page or in an application or based on other non-personal information.

We and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with us more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you the next time you visit the store. Knowing your country and language helps us provide a customized and more useful shopping experience. Knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain product or used a particular service helps us make our advertising and email communications more relevant to your interests.

If you want to disable cookies and you’re using a computer web browser, go to preferences and then disable cookies. Check with your provider to find out how to disable cookies. Please note that certain features of our website may not be available once cookies are disabled.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on our website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

Disclosure to Third Parties  
At times we may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with us to provide products and services, or that help us market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by us to provide or improve our products, services and advertising; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

Service Providers  
We share personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever we operate.

Others  
It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for us to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

Protection of Personal Information  
We take the security of your personal information very seriously. Our online services such as the store protect your personal information during transit using encryption such as Transport Layer Security (TLS). When your personal data is stored by us, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures.

When you use some of our products, services, or applications or post on our forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

Integrity and Retention of Personal Information  
We make it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

Access to Personal Information  
You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with access for any purpose including to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if we are not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made through the regional Privacy Contact Form.

Location-Based Services  
To provide location-based services on our products, we and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by us and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, we may share geographic location with application providers when you opt in to their location services.

Some location-based services offered by us, may require your personal information for the feature to work.

Third-Party Sites and Services  
Our websites, products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties − for example, a third-party product. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

International Users  
All the information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy.

Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy  
To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to our employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

Privacy Questions  
If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please contact us.

All such communications are examined and replies issued where appropriate as soon as possible. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received, you may refer your complaint to the relevant regulator in your jurisdiction. If you ask us, we will endeavor to provide you with information about relevant complaint avenues which may be applicable to your circumstances.

We may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

**Use of cookies**  
General Magic B.V. (Company).

Company websites and online services may use “cookies.” Cookies enable you to use shopping carts and to personalize your experience on our sites, tell us which parts of Company websites people have visited, help Company measure the effectiveness of ads and web searches, and give Company insights into user behavior so Company can improve our communications and products.

Check with your provider’s web browser to find out how to disable cookies. Because cookies are used throughout our websites, disabling them may prevent you from using certain parts of the sites.

The cookies used on Company websites have been categorized based on the guidelines found in the ICC UK Cookie guide. Company uses the following categories on our websites and other online services:

Category 1 — Strictly Necessary Cookies  
These cookies are essential to enable you to browse around our websites and use their features. Without these cookies, services like shopping baskets and e-billing cannot be provided.

Category 2 — Performance Cookies  
These cookies collect information about how you use our websites — for instance, which pages you go to most. This data may be used to help optimize our websites and make them easier for you to navigate. These cookies are also used to let affiliates know if you came to one of our websites from an affiliate and if your visit resulted in the use or purchase of a product or service from us, including details of the product or service purchased. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.

Category 3 — Functionality Cookies  
These cookies allow our websites to remember choices you make while browsing. For instance, we may store your geographic location in a cookie to ensure that we show you our website localized for your area. We may also remember preferences such as text size, fonts, and other customizable site elements. They may also be used to keep track of what featured products or videos have been viewed to avoid repetition. The information these cookies collect will not personally identify you, and they cannot track your browsing activity on non-Company websites.

**Website terms of use**  
General Magic B.V. (Company)

Ownership of Site; Agreement to Terms of Use

These Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms of Use”) apply to the Company web sites, and all associated sites by Company, its subsidiaries and affiliates, including Company sites around the world (collectively, the “Site”). The Site is the property of Company and its licensors. BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE; IF YOU DO NOT AGREE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.

Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Use, at any time. It is your responsibility to check these Terms of Use periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, Company grants you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use the Site.

Content  
All text, graphics, user interfaces, visual interfaces, photographs, trademarks, logos, sounds, music, artwork and computer code (collectively, “Content”), including but not limited to the design, structure, selection, coordination, expression, “look and feel” and arrangement of such Content, contained on the Site is owned, controlled or licensed by or to Company, and is protected by trade dress, copyright, patent and trademark laws, and various other intellectual property rights and unfair competition laws.

Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, no part of the Site and no Content may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, publicly displayed, encoded, translated, transmitted or distributed in any way (including “mirroring”) to any other computer, server, Web site or other medium for publication or distribution or for any commercial enterprise, without Company’s express prior written consent.

You may use information on Company products and services (such as data sheets, support articles, and similar materials) purposely made available by Company for downloading from the Site, provided that you (1) not remove any proprietary notice language in all copies of such documents, (2) use such information only for your personal, non-commercial informational purpose and do not copy or post such information on any networked computer or broadcast it in any media, (3) make no modifications to any such information, and (4) not make any additional representations or warranties relating to such documents.

Your Use of the Site  
You may not use any “deep-link”, “page-scrape”, “robot”, “spider” or other automatic device, program, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor any portion of the Site or any Content, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Site or any Content, to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or information through any means not purposely made available through the Site. Company reserves the right to bar any such activity.

You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Site, or any other systems or networks connected to the Site or to any Company server, or to any of the services offered on or through the Site, by hacking, password “mining” or any other illegitimate means.

You may not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Site or any network connected to the Site, nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Site or any network connected to the Site. You may not reverse look-up, trace or seek to trace any information on any other user of or visitor to the Site, or any other customer of Company, including any Company account not owned by you, to its source, or exploit the Site or any service or information made available or offered by or through the Site, in any way where the purpose is to reveal any information, including but not limited to personal identification or information, other than your own information, as provided for by the Site.

You agree that you will not take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the infrastructure of the Site or Company’s systems or networks, or any systems or networks connected to the Site or to Company.

You agree not to use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Site or any transaction being conducted on the Site, or with any other person’s use of the Site.

You may not forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any message or transmittal you send to Company on or through the Site or any service offered on or through the Site. You may not pretend that you are, or that you represent, someone else, or impersonate any other individual or entity.

You may not use the Site or any Content for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use, or to solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity which infringes the rights of Company or others.

Purchases; Other Terms and Conditions  
Additional terms and conditions may apply to purchases of goods or services and to specific portions or features of the Site, including contests, promotions or other similar features, all of which terms are made a part of these Terms of Use by this reference. You agree to abide by such other terms and conditions, including where applicable representing that you are of sufficient legal age to use or participate in such service or feature. If there is a conflict between these Terms of Use and the terms posted for or applicable to a specific portion of the Site or for any service offered on or through the Site, the latter terms shall control with respect to your use of that portion of the Site or the specific service.

Company’s obligations, if any, with regard to its products and services are governed solely by the agreements pursuant to which they are provided, and nothing on this Site should be construed to alter such agreements.

Company may make changes to any products or services offered on the Site, or to the applicable prices for any such products or services, at any time, without notice. The materials on the Site with respect to products and services may be out of date, and Company makes no commitment to update the materials on the Site with respect to such products and services.

The following terms also govern and apply to your use of the Site, and they are incorporated herein by this reference:

• Guidelines for Using Company Trademarks & Copyrights  
• Rights & Permissions  
• Trademarks  
• Claims of Copyright Infringement  
• Piracy  
• Counterfeit Products  
• Software License Information  
• Legal Contacts

Each of these policies may be changed from time to time and are effective immediately upon posting such changes on the Site.

Accounts, Passwords and Security  
Certain features or services offered on or through the Site may require you to open an account (including setting up an Company ID and password). You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the information you hold for your account, including your password, and for any and all activity that occurs under your account as a result of your failing to keep this information secure and confidential. You agree to notify Company immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password, or any other breach of security. You may be held liable for losses incurred by Company or any other user of or visitor to the Site due to someone else using your Company ID, password or account as a result of your failing to keep your account information secure and confidential.

You may not use anyone else’s Company ID, password or account at any time without the express permission and consent of the holder of that Company ID, password or account. Company cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with these obligations.

Privacy  
Company’s Privacy Policy applies to use of this Site, and its terms are made a part of these Terms of Use by this reference. To view Company’s Privacy Policy, click here. Additionally, by using the Site, you acknowledge and agree that Internet transmissions are never completely private or secure. You understand that any message or information you send to the Site may be read or intercepted by others, even if there is a special notice that a particular transmission (for example, credit card information) is encrypted.

Links to Other Sites and to the Company Site  
This Site may contain links to other independent third-party Web sites (“Linked Sites”). These Linked Sites are provided solely as a convenience to our visitors. Such Linked Sites are not under Company’s control, and Company is not responsible for and does not endorse the content of such Linked Sites, including any information or materials contained on such Linked Sites. You will need to make your own independent judgment regarding your interaction with these Linked Sites.

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your privacy when using our website is extremely important to us. Below we inform you in detail about our policy on processing personal data, as well as anonymous data.

This privacy policy discloses policies and procedures regarding the information we process from or about our customers / people and the use of our products and services.

General Magic Technology S.R.L., Romanian legal entity, based in Brasov, Gheorghe Lazar str. 2, Jud. Braşov, registered with the Brasov Trade Register under No. J8/518/15.03.2017, tax code RO 37212720, as Operator (hereinafter referred to as "Operator"), intends to provide you with an adequate level of comfort and confidence in the way we process and protect the information we collect.

1\. How we use the personal data  
In this section you will find information about:  
a. The categories of personal data that we process;  
b. The source of personal data, if personal data was not obtained directly from the person concerned;  
c. The purposes of processing personal data.

The operator processes the following categories of data:  
a. Name and surname  
b. Place and date of birth  
c. Personal numerical code  
d. Home/residence/postal address  
e. Citizenship  
f. Data on Identity document (number, serial, validity, issuing institution)  
g. Bank account  
h. Signature  
i. Telephone number  
j. Email address  
k. Information on logging into the applications made available by the Operator  
l. Data of geolocation collected by GPS  
m. Email address  
n. Billing address  
o. Bank card data  
p. Telephone number  
q. Fax number  
r. IP address (static/dynamic)  
s. MAC address  
t. Log data  
u. Cookies.

This website uses cookies to improve your browsing experience and to provide you with personalized services, based on your previous choices.

Our privacy policy applies only to data collected through the website. General Magic Technology SRL does not accepts any liability for data collected by other websites accessed by you at the same time or via links accessed from our website.

The source of the processed personal data is www.magicearth.com.

This personal data will only be processed for the following purposes:  
a. To sell you any product and/or service of General Magic Technology S.R.L as a result of registration on our website  
b. For marketing purposes (such as contacting you, including by post, e-mail, fax, text or telephone, in connection with our offer of goods or services)  
c. For conducting market surveys to determine the satisfaction of clients, to produce statistical reports  
d. For contacting the Operator via one of the email addresses within the website: info@generalmagic.com, sales@generalmagic.com, marketing@generalmagic.com, press@generalmagic.com, support@generalmagic.com, careers@generalmagic.com

The legal basis for this processing is the legitimate consent or interests of the Operator, namely: the sale of Operator's products/services, market research, marketing purposes, recruitment of personnel, press communications, technical assistance services provided to clients.

Transfer of personal data  
Your personal data:  
• will not be transferred to other States  
• will be transferred to entities in the same group as the Operator

Also, in order to provide you with our products and services, we may transfer your personal data to entities within our group, to our partners who ensure an adequate level of protection of personal data, according to the protection standards in force.

In addition to the above, data will not be passed on to other third parties, such as marketing databases or direct marketing companies.  
In addition to the above disclosures, we may disclose your personal data to the authorities if this disclosure is necessary to comply with a legal obligation to which we are subject or to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another individual. We may also disclose your personal data if such disclosure is necessary for the determination, exercise or defense of legal claims, either in court proceedings or in an administrative or extrajudicial procedure.

The hosting facilities for our web site are located in Romania.

2\. Retention of personal data  
We will keep your personal data as long as it is necessary to achieve the processing purposes mentioned in point 1 above, unless a longer period of time is required by law. Without prejudice to the other provisions of this section, we may retain your personal data when storage is required to comply with a legal obligation to which we are subject or to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another individual.  
Once your processing operations have ceased, your personal data will be destroyed by processes that do not allow their reconstitution or anonymized.

3\. Amendments  
Following the legislative changes or the intervening of new operational situations, we may periodically update this policy by publishing a new version on our website, so that the personal data processing policy is in line with legal requirements.  
In this regard, we recommend that you check this page occasionally to make sure that you are aware of the latest version of the Personal Data Processing Policy.  
We will notify you of the changes made to this policy via email or via the private messaging system on our website.

4\. Your Rights  
In this section, we have summarized your rights under the personal data protection legislation. Some rights are complex and not all the details have been included in our summaries. Therefore, we recommend that you read the relevant laws and guidelines from the regulatory authority for a full explanation of these rights.

Your main rights under the personal data protection legislation are:  
a. Right of access - the right to obtain from the Operator a confirmation whether it is processing your personal data or not and, if so, access to that data, together with certain additional information. This additional information shall include details on the purpose of processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data. If the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will provide you with a copy of your personal data. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable charge based on administrative costs.

b. Right to rectification - the right to obtain from the Operator, without undue delay, the rectification of the inaccurate personal data concerning you.

c. Right to delete data (the right to be forgotten) - the right to obtain from the Operator the deletion of personal data concerning you without undue delay and the Operator has the obligation to delete personal data without unjustified delay in the cases expressly provided for by the personal data protection legislation. These circumstances include:  
• Personal data are no longer required in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed  
• You withdraw your consent for consent-based processing  
• You object the processing in accordance with certain rules of the applicable personal data protection law  
• Processing is for direct marketing purposes  
• Personal data has been processed illegally

However, there are exclusions of the right of deletion, to the extent that the processing is necessary:  
• To exercise the right to freedom of expression and information  
• To comply with a legal obligation  
• To establish, exercise or defend legal claims

d. Right to obtain the restriction of the processing - the right to obtain from the Operator the restriction of the processing in the express cases provided by the legislation on the personal data protection. These circumstances include:  
• Appeal to the accuracy of personal data  
• Processing is illegal, but you object deletion  
• We no longer need personal data for the purpose of processing, but you need personal data for establishing, exercising or defending legal claims  
• You opposed the processing

If processing has been restricted on this basis, such personal data may, with the exception of storage, be processed only with your consent or for the establishment, exercise or defense of a right in court or for the protection of the rights of another individual or legal reasons, or for reasons of public interest of the Union or of a Member State.

e. Right to objection - the right to oppose the processing, on grounds relating to the particular situation in which you are under the personal data protection law, including the creation of profiles;  
You may oppose the processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease processing your personal data for that purpose.

f. Right to portability - the right to receive personal data concerning you that you have provided to the Operator in a structured format. You have the right to transmit this data to another operator under the express conditions provided by the data protection legislation;

g. Right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority;

h. Right to withdraw your consent.  
You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data in any of the following ways: submitting a written notice, in physical format addressed to General Magic Technology with the postal address Brasov, str. Gheorghe Lazar 2, Jud. Braşov, or electronically to the email address info@generalmagic.com.

5\. Data security  
a. Identification and authentication. The Operator operates in accordance with the legal requirements. Access to personal data is allowed only to authorized personnel, provided by a person designated specifically for this purpose, acting solely on the basis of instructions received from the Operator.

b. Empowered persons have access to personal data on the basis of passwords. Password management measures and control measures are implemented, including the minimum length of the password, as well as the obligation to periodically change passwords and not to reuse old passwords. All passwords are treated as sensitive and confidential information.

c. Data collection. Personal data is collected and entered into the database by individuals specifically designated for this purpose.

d. Access in the building and to the computers. The building is guarded by qualified personnel and video surveillance. The use of computers is subject to authentication based on the used passwords.

e. The training of the staff authorized by the Operator. The authorized personnel shall be regularly informed of the security policies and procedures for the processing of personal data.

f. Data printing. The right to print data from personal databases is limited only to authorized personnel and only for the performance of their service duties.

g. The security policy for the personal data processing is complemented by the protection system by the fact that:  
• All electronic equipment and resources are adequately protected. Access to them is allowed only to authorized persons.  
• Authorized personnel have been instructed not to leave computers unattended as long as they are in operation and connected to a particular application.

The operator has implemented computer access surveillance solutions and devices, such as password protection.

6\. About us  
This website is owned and operated by General Magic Technology.  
You can contact us by any of the following ways:  
• by post, at postal address Romania, Gheorghe Lazar nr. 2, 500090, Brasov  
• by using the contact form of our website  
• by email, at info@generalmagic.com

You can get a copy of the stored information by addressing an email request to the address above.

**Use of cookies**

Company websites and online services may use “cookies.” Cookies enable you to use shopping carts and to personalize your experience on our sites, tell us which parts of Company websites people have visited, help Company measure the effectiveness of ads and web searches, and give Company insights into user behavior so Company can improve our communications and products.

Check with your provider’s web browser to find out how to disable cookies. Because cookies are used throughout our websites, disabling them may prevent you from using certain parts of the sites.

The cookies used on Company websites have been categorized based on the guidelines found in the ICC UK Cookie guide. Company uses the following categories on our websites and other online services:

Category 1 — Strictly Necessary Cookies  
These cookies are essential to enable you to browse around our websites and use their features. Without these cookies, services like shopping baskets and e-billing cannot be provided.

Category 2 — Performance Cookies  
These cookies collect information about how you use our websites — for instance, which pages you go to most. This data may be used to help optimize our websites and make them easier for you to navigate. These cookies are also used to let affiliates know if you came to one of our websites from an affiliate and if your visit resulted in the use or purchase of a product or service from us, including details of the product or service purchased. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.

Category 3 — Functionality Cookies  
These cookies allow our websites to remember choices you make while browsing. For instance, we may store your geographic location in a cookie to ensure that we show you our website localized for your area. We may also remember preferences such as text size, fonts, and other customizable site elements. They may also be used to keep track of what featured products or videos have been viewed to avoid repetition. The information these cookies collect will not personally identify you, and they cannot track your browsing activity on non-Company websites.

**Website terms of use**

Ownership of Site; Agreement to Terms of Use

These Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms of Use”) apply to the Company web sites, and all associated sites by Company, its subsidiaries and affiliates, including Company sites around the world (collectively, the “Site”). The Site is the property of Company and its licensors. BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE; IF YOU DO NOT AGREE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.

Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms of Use, at any time. It is your responsibility to check these Terms of Use periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes will mean that you accept and agree to the changes. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, Company grants you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use the Site.

Content  
All text, graphics, user interfaces, visual interfaces, photographs, trademarks, logos, sounds, music, artwork and computer code (collectively, “Content”), including but not limited to the design, structure, selection, coordination, expression, “look and feel” and arrangement of such Content, contained on the Site is owned, controlled or licensed by or to Company, and is protected by trade dress, copyright, patent and trademark laws, and various other intellectual property rights and unfair competition laws.

Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, no part of the Site and no Content may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, publicly displayed, encoded, translated, transmitted or distributed in any way (including “mirroring”) to any other computer, server, Web site or other medium for publication or distribution or for any commercial enterprise, without Company’s express prior written consent.

You may use information on Company products and services (such as data sheets, support articles, and similar materials) purposely made available by Company for downloading from the Site, provided that you (1) not remove any proprietary notice language in all copies of such documents, (2) use such information only for your personal, non-commercial informational purpose and do not copy or post such information on any networked computer or broadcast it in any media, (3) make no modifications to any such information, and (4) not make any additional representations or warranties relating to such documents.

Your Use of the Site  
You may not use any “deep-link”, “page-scrape”, “robot”, “spider” or other automatic device, program, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor any portion of the Site or any Content, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Site or any Content, to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or information through any means not purposely made available through the Site. Company reserves the right to bar any such activity.

You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Site, or any other systems or networks connected to the Site or to any Company server, or to any of the services offered on or through the Site, by hacking, password “mining” or any other illegitimate means.

You may not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Site or any network connected to the Site, nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Site or any network connected to the Site. You may not reverse look-up, trace or seek to trace any information on any other user of or visitor to the Site, or any other customer of Company, including any Company account not owned by you, to its source, or exploit the Site or any service or information made available or offered by or through the Site, in any way where the purpose is to reveal any information, including but not limited to personal identification or information, other than your own information, as provided for by the Site.

You agree that you will not take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the infrastructure of the Site or Company’s systems or networks, or any systems or networks connected to the Site or to Company.

You agree not to use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Site or any transaction being conducted on the Site, or with any other person’s use of the Site.

You may not forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any message or transmittal you send to Company on or through the Site or any service offered on or through the Site. You may not pretend that you are, or that you represent, someone else, or impersonate any other individual or entity.

You may not use the Site or any Content for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use, or to solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity which infringes the rights of Company or others.

Purchases; Other Terms and Conditions  
Additional terms and conditions may apply to purchases of goods or services and to specific portions or features of the Site, including contests, promotions or other similar features, all of which terms are made a part of these Terms of Use by this reference. You agree to abide by such other terms and conditions, including where applicable representing that you are of sufficient legal age to use or participate in such service or feature. If there is a conflict between these Terms of Use and the terms posted for or applicable to a specific portion of the Site or for any service offered on or through the Site, the latter terms shall control with respect to your use of that portion of the Site or the specific service.

Company’s obligations, if any, with regard to its products and services are governed solely by the agreements pursuant to which they are provided, and nothing on this Site should be construed to alter such agreements.

Company may make changes to any products or services offered on the Site, or to the applicable prices for any such products or services, at any time, without notice. The materials on the Site with respect to products and services may be out of date, and Company makes no commitment to update the materials on the Site with respect to such products and services.

The following terms also govern and apply to your use of the Site, and they are incorporated herein by this reference:

• Guidelines for Using Company Trademarks & Copyrights  
• Rights & Permissions  
• Trademarks  
• Claims of Copyright Infringement  
• Piracy  
• Counterfeit Products  
• Software License Information  
• Legal Contacts

Each of these policies may be changed from time to time and are effective immediately upon posting such changes on the Site.

Accounts, Passwords and Security  
Certain features or services offered on or through the Site may require you to open an account (including setting up an Company ID and password). You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the information you hold for your account, including your password, and for any and all activity that occurs under your account as a result of your failing to keep this information secure and confidential. You agree to notify Company immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password, or any other breach of security. You may be held liable for losses incurred by Company or any other user of or visitor to the Site due to someone else using your Company ID, password or account as a result of your failing to keep your account information secure and confidential.

You may not use anyone else’s Company ID, password or account at any time without the express permission and consent of the holder of that Company ID, password or account. Company cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with these obligations.

Privacy  
Company’s Privacy Policy applies to use of this Site, and its terms are made a part of these Terms of Use by this reference. Additionally, by using the Site, you acknowledge and agree that Internet transmissions are never completely private or secure. You understand that any message or information you send to the Site may be read or intercepted by others, even if there is a special notice that a particular transmission (for example, credit card information) is encrypted.

Links to Other Sites and to the Company Site  
This Site may contain links to other independent third-party Web sites (“Linked Sites”). These Linked Sites are provided solely as a convenience to our visitors. Such Linked Sites are not under Company’s control, and Company is not responsible for and does not endorse the content of such Linked Sites, including any information or materials contained on such Linked Sites. You will need to make your own independent judgment regarding your interaction with these Linked Sites.

* * *

Type and Press “enter” to Search
